http://www.edgarcayce.org/about-us/privacy-policy-statement/

back
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Headquarter Conferences
Conferences Near You (U.S. Cities)
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
back
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Headquarter Conferences
Conferences Near You (U.S. Cities)
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
back
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Headquarter Conferences
Conferences Near You (U.S. Cities)
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
back
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
back
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
back
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Items
Cart Total:
Checkout
x
Details
Attendee :
Badge Name:
Member Number:
Discounts: $
View/Edit your Cart
Your cart is empty.
Mind
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Headquarter Conferences
Conferences Near You (U.S. Cities)
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
Body
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Headquarter Conferences
Conferences Near You (U.S. Cities)
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
Spirit
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Headquarter Conferences
Conferences Near You (U.S. Cities)
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
Edgar Cayce
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
Edgar Cayce Reflections Show
Edgar Cayce TV (YouTube)
Visit
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
About Us
Crisis Resources: What Can I Do?
GO
A.R.E.
About Us
Privacy Policy Statement
Privacy Policy Statement
Our physical address is:215 67th StreetVirginia Beach, VA 23451
Use our Contact Us form to send us any issues or feedback, or you can reach us by telephone at 757-428-3588.
Your PrivacyEdgar Cayce’s Association for Research and Enlightenment (A.R.E.) believes in protecting the integrity and privacy of personal information gathered from our members and from visitors to our websites. Because protecting your privacy is of great importance to us, we have created this privacy policy to communicate our practices regarding the collection and dissemination of personal information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name, address, phone number, email address, or any other information provided to us by our members and by visitors to our websites.Why does the A.R.E. ask for my information?In order to participate in some activities, you might be asked to provide some personal information. This could be in connection with any one or combination of the following:
Shipping items purchased from the A.R.E. Catalog
Making a donation online
Registering online for A.R.E. Conferences, Tours, Camp events
Participating in contests, surveys, petitions, and giveaways
Requesting information packs
Subscribing to A.R.E. enews list
What information does A.R.E. collect?We do not collect personal information from our visitors other than that which is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.
WebsiteWe collect the aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, and other information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our website and web pages, to customize the content and/or layout of our page(s) for each individual visitor, and/or to notify consumers about updates to our website. Users can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads at Tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
CookiesWhat is a Cookie? A cookie is a small piece of data that is stored on a visitor’s hard drive but does not contain any personal information itself. Cookies enhance a visitor’s experience by preventing the visitor from having to login or provide information each time he or she revisits our EdgarCayce.org website and by customizing content based on a visitor’s interests.We use cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record session information (such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart), record user-specific information on what page(s) users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our website, record past activity at our site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, and customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.
SecurityA.R.E. is extremely protective of the information gathered through its membership and websites. Our websites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. Our Web server is located in a locked, secure environment. When you contribute to A.R.E. online, register for an event, or make a purchase through the A.R.E. Catalog, we use a secure server and encryption to protect your financial and other personal information during transmission.
Member/Donor Privacy PolicyThe A.R.E. does not sell, trade, or share a member/donor's personal information with anyone else, nor do we send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations.
AppsIf you have purchased one of our apps, your name will not be sold to any other organization. We may email you to invite you to join our enews list. If you join our enews list, our email Privacy Policy applies. If you make a purchase from our website, our Mailing Address policy applies.
EmailIf you have signed up for our enews and/or placed an order through our catalog and provided your email address, you will receive regular enews updates from us. If you do not wish to receive email from us in the future, please use the unsubscribe link that is provided at the bottom of every enews that is sent from A.R.E. or by completing our online Contact Us form.
On occasion, Baar Products, our official supplier of Cayce Care remedies products, may also send you an email. However, we will not share your email address with any other outside companies or organizations.
Mailing AddressIf you supply us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events, A.R.E. membership, or Support Our Work mailings. If you do not wish to receive such mailings please let us know by contacting us at the above postal address or telephone number or completing our Contact Us form.
In addition to mailings from our organization, you may receive mailings from other reputable like-minded companies. You can, however, have your name put on our “do-not-rent” list by contacting us at the above postal address or telephone number or completing our online Contact Us form. When doing so, please provide us with your exact name and address.
Telephone NumberIf you supply us with your telephone number(s), we may call you for clarification of details on your order or the status of your membership. We will not share your number with any other companies or organizations.
Ad ServersWe do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
A Final NoteFrom time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by contacting us at the above postal address or telephone number or completing our online Contact Us form.
If at any time you would like to have your information completely removed from A.R.E. records, please send an email to GDPRRequests@EdgarCayce.org.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated policy, please contact us at the above postal address or telephone number or complete our online Contact Us form; or contact the DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at ethics@the-dma.org, or contact your state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau.
×
Reset Password
Email Address
Close
×
Retrieve Your Member / Customer Number
Email Address
Close
